(Sheldon:)Of course it is.
It's the perfect gift.
H-How are you feeling right now?
(Sheldon:)Guilty? Sad?
(Sheldon:)Wishing you were Jewish?
(Amy:)No, I love it.
(Sheldon:)Oh, really?
(Sheldon:)Well, how about now?
(Christmas music playing)
SHELDON (recorded):
Happy holidays to my dear Amy.
(Sheldon:)I hope you treasure this
(Sheldon:)as much as I treasure you.
(mouthing)
(Sheldon:)And you got me nothing.
(Sheldon:)Christmas is ruined.
(Sheldon:)Let's never speak of it again.
(Sheldon:)Well, this was fun.
(Raj:)Actually,
(Amy:)I did get you
something.
(Sheldon:)But what about our agreement?
(Amy:)Well, you got me
something. Here.
(Sheldon:)Cookies?
(Amy:)They're your Meemaw's
Christmas cookies.
(Amy:)I called and got
the recipe.